C. An impassioned circulation of affection
time limit per test
2 seconds
memory limit per test
256 megabytes
input
standard input
output
standard output
Nadeko's birthday is approaching! As she decorated the room for the party, a long garland of Dianthus-shaped paper pieces was placed on a prominent part of the wall. Brother Koyomi will like it!
Still unsatisfied with the garland, Nadeko decided to polish it again. The garland has
n
pieces numbered from
1
to
n
from left to right, and the
i
-th piece has a colour
s
i
, denoted by a lowercase English letter. Nadeko will repaint
at most
m
of the pieces to give each of them an arbitrary new colour (still denoted by a lowercase English letter). After this work, she finds out all subsegments of the garland containing pieces of only colour
c
ÈÃ÷ Brother Koyomi's favourite one, and takes the length of the longest among them to be the
Koyomity
of the garland.
For instance, let's say the garland is represented by "
kooomo
", and Brother Koyomi's favourite colour is "
o
". Among all subsegments containing pieces of "
o
" only, "
ooo
" is the longest, with a length of
3
. Thus the
Koyomity
of this garland equals
3
.
But problem arises as Nadeko is unsure about Brother Koyomi's favourite colour, and has swaying ideas on the amount of work to do. She has
q
plans on this, each of which can be expressed as a pair of an integer
m
i
and a lowercase letter
c
i
, meanings of which are explained above. You are to find out the maximum
Koyomity
achievable after repainting the garland according to each plan.
Input
The first line of input contains a positive integer
n
(
1ÈÃÙÈÙ±ÈÃÙ
n
ÈÃÙÈÙ±ÈÃÙ1ÈÃÙ500
) ÈÃ÷ the length of the garland.
The second line contains
n
lowercase English letters
s
1
s
2
...
s
n
as a string ÈÃ÷ the initial colours of paper pieces on the garland.
The third line contains a positive integer
q
(
1ÈÃÙÈÙ±ÈÃÙ
q
ÈÃÙÈÙ±ÈÃÙ200ÈÃÙ000
) ÈÃ÷ the number of plans Nadeko has.
The next
q
lines describe one plan each: the
i
-th among them contains an integer
m
i
(
1ÈÃÙÈÙ±ÈÃÙ
m
i
ÈÃÙÈÙ±ÈÃÙ
n
) ÈÃ÷ the maximum amount of pieces to repaint, followed by a space, then by a lowercase English letter
c
i
ÈÃ÷ Koyomi's possible favourite colour.
Output
Output
q
lines: for each work plan, output one line containing an integer ÈÃ÷ the largest
Koyomity
achievable after repainting the garland according to it.
Examples
Input
Copy
6
koyomi
3
1 o
4 o
4 m
Output
Copy
3
6
5
Input
Copy
15
yamatonadeshiko
10
1 a
2 a
3 a
4 a
5 a
1 b
2 b
3 b
4 b
5 b
Output
Copy
3
4
5
7
8
1
2
3
4
5
Input
Copy
10
aaaaaaaaaa
2
10 b
10 z
Output
Copy
10
10
Note
In the first sample, there are three plans:
In the first plan, at most
1
piece can be repainted. Repainting the "
y
" piece to become "
o
" results in "
kooomi
", whose
Koyomity
of
3
is the best achievable;
In the second plan, at most
4
pieces can be repainted, and "
oooooo
" results in a
Koyomity
of
6
;
In the third plan, at most
4
pieces can be repainted, and "
mmmmmi
" and "
kmmmmm
" both result in a
Koyomity
of
5
.
